Guide to the Walter E. Fauntroy papers, 1941-1990 MS2070
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- General files, 1960-1990; MS2070 Series 1; 9 Linear feet
  - News Releases, Emergency Legislative Powers, 1980 June 06 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - News Releases, Federal Payment, 1980 June 17 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - News Releases, Politics and Religion, 1980 October 16 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - News Releases, El Salvador, 1981 January 11 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - News Releases, 97th Congress, 1981 January 24 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - News Releases, General Obligation Bonds, 1981 February 05 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - News Releases, House Resolution 41, 1981 March 04 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - News Releases, Mid-year Report, 1981 July 30 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - News Releases, Crime Report, 1981 August 19 (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - News Releases, Arms Bazzar, 1981 September 10 (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - News Releases, Push Excel Grant, 1981 September 15 (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - News Releases, Credit Market, 1981 October 14 (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - News Releases, "RIF", 1981 October 22-1982 June 24 (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - News Releases, Crime Reduction Campaign, 1981 November 12 (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - News Releases, Air and Rail Accidents, 1982 January 13 (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - News Releases, Arts and Business Community, 1982 January 18 (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - News Releases, House Resolution 365, 1982 January 25 (Box 15, Folder 27)
  - News Releases, Fauntroy Birthday Celebration, 1982 February 24 (Box 15, Folder 28)
  - News Releases, Freeze on Nuclear Weapons, 1982 March 26 (Box 15, Folder 29)
  - News Releases, Committee on Printing, 1982 May 25 (Box 15, Folder 30)
  - News Releases, D.C. Elderly, 1982 May 28 (Box 15, Folder 31)
  - News Releases, Drug Parapheinalia, 1982 June 04 (Box 15, Folder 32)
  - News Releases, Jewish Community Council, 1982 June 23 (Box 15, Folder 33)
  - News Releases, Budget Amendment, 1982 July 19 (Box 15, Folder 34)
  - News Releases, Student Loans, 1982 July 29 (Box 15, Folder 35)
  - News Releases, Small Business Administration, 1982 August 11 (Box 15, Folder 36)
  - News Releases, Lorton Operation, 1982 September 02 (Box 15, Folder 37)
  - News Releases, Child Run Aways, 1982 September 09 (Box 15, Folder 38)
  - News Releases, Corporate Take Over, 1982 September 12 (Box 15, Folder 39)
  - News Releases, Media Boycott, 1982 September 14 (Box 15, Folder 40)
  - News Releases, Hault P.C.B., 1982 September 21 (Box 15, Folder 41)
  - News Releases, Convention Center, 1982 September 30 (Box 15, Folder 42)
  - News Releases, "Back On Track", 1982 October 20 (Box 15, Folder 43)
  - News Releases, Response to Klan, 1982 November 23 (Box 15, Folder 44)
  - News Releases, Foster Children's Christmas Party, 1982 December 10 (Box 15, Folder 45)
  - News Releases, Waste Siting Discrimination, 1982 December 14 (Box 15, Folder 46)
  - News Releases, Press Kits for 98th Congress, 1983 (Box 15, Folder 47)
  - News Releases, Clara Barton Parkway, undated (Box 15, Folder 48)
  - News Releases, Cultural Meeting, undated (Box 15, Folder 49)
  - News Releases, Green Line Metro, undated (Box 15, Folder 50)
  - News Releases, House Resolution 1310, undated (Box 15, Folder 51)
  - News Releases, New Jobs, undated (Box 15, Folder 52)
  - Transcripts, Radio Program, Radio TV Reports, Inc., 1968 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Transcripts, "Capitol Comment", 1975 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Transcripts, "Capitol Comment", 1976 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Transcripts, "Capitol Comment", 1977 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Transcripts, "Capitol Comment", 1978 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Subject reference files: Africa, West Africa Drought, 1973 July 09 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Subject reference files: Africa, West Africa Famine, 1973 November 29 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Subject reference files: Africa, South Africa, 1982-1990 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Subject reference files: Africa, Nambia, 1982 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Subject reference files: Africa, Zimbabwe, 1984 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Subject reference files: Africa, Nigeria, 1990 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Subject reference files: Africa, Niger, undated (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Subject reference files: Agriculture, U.S. Agriculture Department, 1965 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Subject reference files: Black Empowerment, Black United Front, 1968 April-1968 May (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Subject reference files: Black Empowerment, Black Land Movement, 1969 March 03 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Subject reference files: Education, D.C. Board of Education, 1970 July 02 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Subject reference files: Education, Howard University, 1973 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Subject reference files: Education, Howard University, 1983 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Subject reference files: Education, Howard University, 1988 (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Subject reference files: Education, Oberlin College, 1974 (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - Subject reference files: Education, Purdue University, undated (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - Subject reference files: Football, Washington Redskins, 1982-1983 (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - Subject reference files: Housing, Ad Hoc Committee on Housing Crisis, 1965 (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - Subject reference files: Housing, D.C. Housing Industry Corp., undated (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - Subject reference files: International Finance, African Development Fund, 1988 May (Box 16, Folder 25)
  - Subject reference files: International Finance, African Development Bank, 1988 May (Box 16, Folder 26)
  - Subject reference files: International Finance, African Development Bank, 1988 May (Box 16, Folder 27)
  - Subject reference files: International Finance, African Development Bank, 1988 (Box 16, Folder 28)
  - Subject reference files: Jackson, Jesse, Media Coverage, 1984-1990 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Subject reference files: Jackson, Jesse, Presidential Campaign, 1984 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Subject reference files: Jackson, Jesse, Presidential Campaign, 1988 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Subject reference files: King, Martin Luther, Media Coverage, 1969-1989 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Subject reference files: King, Martin Luther, Motion Picture Story, 1970 March 24 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Subject reference files: King, Martin Luther, Beyond Vietnam, Circa 1982 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Subject reference files: King, Martin Luther, The Leader and the Legacy, 1986 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Subject reference files: King, Martin Luther, MLK Holiday Activites, 1988 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Subject reference files: King, Martin Luther, Holiday Commission, 1989 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Subject reference files: King, Martin Luther, National Memorial Committee, 1989 July 17 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Subject reference files: King, Martin Luther, Federal Holiday Commission Bill, 1989 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Subject reference files: Legislation, How Our Laws Are Made, 1963 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Subject reference files: Legislation, Legislative Initiatives, 1983 January 27 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Subject reference files: Legislation, Program and Timetable, 99th Congress, 1983-1984 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Subject reference files: Legislation, Armed Forces House Resolution 2169, 1987 April 27 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Subject reference files: Legislation, Environmental Issues House Resolution 2452, 1987 May 18 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Subject reference files: Legislation, Education House Resolution 5, 1987 June 03 (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Subject reference files: Legislation, House Resolution 2714 Appropriations for the Legislative Branch, 1987-1988 (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - Subject reference files: Legislation, Transition Committee, 1988 (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - Subject reference files: Legislation, Whip Nomination, Circa 1988 (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - Subject reference files: Legislation, 101st Congress Plan, Circa 1989 (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - Subject reference files: Legislation, 101st Congressional Files, 1990 (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - Subject reference files: Legislation, Congressional District Legislative Meeting, 1992 January 30 (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - Subject reference files: Legislation, Card, WEF's Legislative Support Network, undated (Box 17, Folder 24)
  - Subject reference files: Literacy, Accelerated Progressive Choice Reading Program Proposal, 1965 February 03 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Subject reference files: Literacy, Accelerated Progressive Choice Reading Program Fact Sheet, undated (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Subject reference files: Literacy, Accelerated Progressive Choice Reading Program Booklets, undated (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Subject reference files: Literacy, Accelerated Progressive Choice Reading Program Booklets, undated (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Subject reference files: NAACP, Overground Railroad, 1984 March (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Subject reference files: Police, Police-Community Relations, 1968 July 26 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Subject reference files: Police, Neighborhood Control of the Police in the Black Community, 1968 September 25 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Subject reference files: Police, Louis G. Stokes Incident, 1983 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Subject reference files: Police, Instructions for Precinct Captain, undated (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Subject reference files: Political Organizations, National Black Political Convention, 1972 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Subject reference files: Racial Issues, Walter Dawson, 1943-1962 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Subject reference files: Racial Issues, Home Visit Day, 1963 November 01-1964 April 19 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Subject reference files: Racial Issues, Racial Justice Act, 1988 April 21 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Subject reference files: Racial Issues, FAIRMICCO Inc., undated (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Subject reference files: Racial Issues, Minorities and the Media, undated (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Subject reference files: Urban Renewal, "No Slums in Ten Years", 1955 January (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Subject reference files: Urban Renewal, Office of Urban Renewal, 1960 September 15-December (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Subject reference files: Urban Renewal, Housing and Home Finance Agency, 1961 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Subject reference files: Urban Renewal, Model Cities Commission Meeting, 1970-1971 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Subject reference files: Urban Renewal, Model Cities Commission Meeting, 1972 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Subject reference files: Urban Renewal, D.C. Redevelopment Land Agency, undated (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Subject reference files: Urban Renewal, Inner City Program Plymouth United Church of Christ, undated (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - newsletters: Near East Report, Report from the Capital, and Western Voice, 1969-1976; Series 1 (Box 60, Folder 1)
  - newsletter; Capital Baptist, 1968-1974; Series 1 (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - newsletter: Capital Baptist, 1975-1977; Series 1 (Box 60, Folder 3)
  - Washington Center for Metropolitan studies notes, 1964; Series 1 (Box 60, Folder 4)
  - Flyer: Dr. Martin Luther King Jr. in Detroit, 1964 October 30; Series 1 (Box 60, Folder 5)
  - D.C. Council records, 1990; Series 1 (Box 60, Folder 6)
  - D.C. Council records, 1989-1990; Series 1 (Box 60, Folder 7)
  - D.C. Council records, 1990; Series 1 (Box 60, Folder 8)
  - National Consumer Cooperative Bank self-development fund, 1982; Series 1 (Box 61, Folder 1)
  - Dixwell Avenue Church historical records, 1957-1959; Series 1 (Box 61, Folder 2)
  - Records related to March on Washington [probably for Special Collections exhibit], 1963-1988; Series 1 (Box 61, Folder 3)
  - Records related to March on Washington [probably for Special Collections exhibit], 1963-2000; Series 1 (Box 61, Folder 4)
  - Buttons used in Special Collections exhibit for March on Washington, Undated; Series 1 (Box 61, Folder 5)
- Affiliations and organization files, 1940-1989; MS2070 Series 2; 6 Linear feet
  This series contains constitutions, correspondence, minutes, proposals and programs from organizations, such as the Baptist Ministers Conference and the YMCA, By-laws and constitutions, activities files, agendas, announcements, articles, background material, booklets, brochures, clippings, contracts, flyers, financial statements, meetings, memorandums, minutes, newsletters, notes, pamphlets, plans, press releases, presentations, program files, proposals, reports, resolutions, statements, subject reference files and workshop files. This material covers the dates 1940-89. These materials relate to or produced by organizations that Fauntroy founded, chaired or maintained memberships within. Some of these organizations include: AFRICARE, Health and Welfare Council -The National Capital Area, Shaw Urban Renewal, Southern Christian, Leadership Conference, March on Washington, and Council of Churches of Greater Washington.
  - General files: Constitutions and By-laws, Baptist Ministers Conference, 1940 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - General files: Campaign Files, World Food Day Convocation, 1988 October 16 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - General files: Campaign Files, WEF Mission Team and Task Force, 1989 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - General files: Correspondence, Task Force on Urban Problems Conference of National Organizations, 1965 July 14 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - General files: Correspondence, Afro American Bicentennial Corporation, 1971 July 23 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - General files: Correspondence, District of Columbia Sportsman League, 1983 March 14 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - General files: Correspondence, Big Brothers, 1984 February (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - General files: Correspondence, Congressional Arts Caucus, 1984 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - General files: Correspondence, Boys and Girls Clubs of Greater Washington, 1989 March 07 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - General files: Program, Southern Rural Action Institute, 1974-1975 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - General files: Program, Prince Hall Freemason and Eastern Star Charitable Foundation of D.C., 1988 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - General files: Meeting Files, Commissioners Crime Council Agenda, 1962 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - General files: Meeting Files, Council of Churches, 1964-1968 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - General files: Meeting Files, YMCA, 1964-1967 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - General files: Meeting Files, Convention II, Founder's Committee, 1984-1988 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - General files: Meeting Files, National Board Committee on Education, Training and Youth, 1988 May 11 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - General files: Meeting Files, D.C. Citizen's Committee, undated (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Africare: Organizatioscription, AFRICARE, undated (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Africare: Clippings, African Drought, 1973 June 21-December 24 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Africare: Correspondence, Drought, 1973 July 13 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Africare: Correspondence, Board of Trustees, 1975-1990 July 02 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Africare: Correspondence, AFRICARE Week, 1983 May 06 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Africare: Flyer, AFRICARE Water Resource Development, undated (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Africare: Invitation, AFRICARE Distinguished Service Awards, 1983 May (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Africare: Meeting Files, African Famine, 1973 July 09 (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Africare: Meeting Files, AFRICARE National Conference, 1974 January 15-1976 February (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Africare: Meeting Files, Board of Directors, 1976 October 08-1982 December 17 (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - Africare: Meeting Files, Briefing Book, 1984 June 15 (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - Africare: Meeting Files, Briefing Book, 1984 June 15 (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - Africare: Meeting Files, Board of Directors Annual Meeting, 1988 June 24 (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - Africare: Newsletter, AFRICARE, Volume 3, Number 2, Spring, 1976 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Africare: Program, "From Allen to Adams" African Methodist Episcopal Church, 1988 April 19-22 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Africare: Report, Trust Fund, Grant, 1975 February-July (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - D.C. Coalition of Conscience: Article, "A Villain to Poor of D.C.?", 1965 May 12 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - D.C. Coalition of Conscience: Correspondence, Public Meeting, 1965 June 07 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - D.C. Coalition of Conscience: Correspondence, St. Augustine, 1964-1965 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - D.C. Coalition of Conscience: Correspondence, Support of Coalition, 1965 May 07 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - D.C. Coalition of Conscience: Correspondence, Russ Connelly, 1965-1966 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - D.C. Coalition of Conscience: Correspondence, David Clarke, 1966-1967 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - D.C. Coalition of Conscience: Meeting Files, Coalition Minutes, 1965 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - D.C. Coalition of Conscience: News Release, Welfare, 1965 April-May (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - D.C. Coalition of Conscience: News Release, D.C. Commissioner Petition, 1965 May (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - D.C. Coalition of Conscience: News Release, Voter Registration and Reconvening of Coalition, 1982 May 15-December 20 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - D.C. Coalition of Conscience: Pamphlet, Hope for the Family, undated (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - D.C. Coalition of Conscience: Programs, Mrs. Mary Etheredge, 1965 April 20-25 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - D.C. Coalition of Conscience: Proposal, Citizens Lobby, undated (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - D.C. Coalition of Conscience: Statement, State of Alabama, 1965 April 21 (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - D.C. Coalition of Conscience: Statement, New Coalition of Conscience, 1983 September 22 (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - D.C. Coalition of Conscience: Statement and Remarks, Welfare, 1965 April-1966 May (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - D.C. Coalition of Conscience: Subject Reference Files, Coalition and Tour of Martin Luther King, Jr., 1965 (Box 21, Folder 20)
  - Fauntroy Family picnic: Clipping, Fauntroy Family Picnic, 1985 August 16 (Box 21, Folder 21)
  - Fauntroy Family picnic: Correspondence, Fauntroy Family Day Picnic, 1961 August 21-1983 July 29 (Box 21, Folder 22)
  - Fauntroy Family picnic: Correspondence, Gerri Williams, 1984 June 15 (Box 21, Folder 23)
  - Fauntroy Family picnic: Correspondence, 7th Annual Picnic, 07/-1985 August (Box 21, Folder 24)
  - Fauntroy Family picnic: Correspondence, 8th Annual Picnic, 1986 May-1986 August (Box 21, Folder 25)
  - Fauntroy Family picnic: Correspondence, 9th Annual Picnic, 1986 January-December (Box 21, Folder 26)
  - Fauntroy Family picnic: Correspondence,l0th Annual Picnic, 1988 June 15 (Box 21, Folder 27)
  - Fauntroy Family picnic: Flyers, 7th, 8th and 9th Annual Picnics, 1985-1987 (Box 21, Folder 28)
  - Fauntroy Family picnic: Program, Fauntroy Family Picnic, 1963 September 25 (Box 21, Folder 29)
  - FIRREA project: Article, Black Enterprise Article Outline on FIRREA, Circa 1989 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - FIRREA project: Briefing Book, FIRREA Project, 1989 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - FIRREA project: Correspondence, William Seidman, 1989 August 22 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Free South Africa Movement: Campaign Files, Boycott Shell, undated (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Free South Africa Movement: Correspondence, Ambassador of Japan from the Free South-Africa Movement, 1987 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Free South Africa Movement: Correspondence, South Africa Mission Team, 1989 March 02 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Free South Africa Movement: Meeting Files, Movement Rally, 1985 February 06 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Free South Africa Movement: News Releases, South African Sanction, 1989 August 01 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Free South Africa Movement: News Releases, Nelson Mandela, undated (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Free South Africa Movement: Speech, South African Sanction Bill, undated (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Free South Africa Movement: Statements, South African Sanctions/South African Loans, 1989 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Health and Welfare Council--The National Capital Area: Booklet, Junior Village Economic Indicators, 1958 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Health and Welfare Council--The National Capital Area: Booklet, Junior Village Dependency, 1959 (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Health and Welfare Council--The National Capital Area: Booklet, The Ineligibles, 1963 (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Health and Welfare Council--The National Capital Area: Booklet, The Public Welfare Crisis in the Nation's Capital, Circa 1963 (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - Health and Welfare Council--The National Capital Area: Booklet, Membership Report, 1964 (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - Health and Welfare Council--The National Capital Area: Brochure, Tutoring, undated (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - Health and Welfare Council--The National Capital Area: Correspondence, Public Welfare Program, 1963 December 23 (Box 22, Folder 18)
  - Health and Welfare Council--The National Capital Area: Correspondence, HWC Delegates Assembly, 1964 April 30 (Box 22, Folder 19)
  - Health and Welfare Council--The National Capital Area: Correspondence, Tutoring Services, 1964 December (Box 22, Folder 20)
  - Howard Thurmond Educational Trust: Booklet, "Freedom Now", undated (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Howard Thurmond Educational Trust: Correspondence, Belva Moore, 1987 March 09 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Howard Thurmond Educational Trust: Financial Statements, 1986 December 31 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Howard Thurmond Educational Trust: Meeting Files, Board of Trustees, 1987 February 14-March 09 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Howard Thurmond Educational Trust: Proposal, Service and Plan of Action, 1967 February (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Howard Thurmond Educational Trust: Report, Development Report, 1987 January (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Howard Thurmond Educational Trust: Report, Annual Report, 1987 February 14 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Martin Luther King Center for Non-Violent Social Change: By-Laws, 1971 June 01 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Martin Luther King Center for Non-Violent Social Change: Correspondence, Coretta Scott King, 1983 February 18 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Martin Luther King Center for Non-Violent Social Change: Flyer, M.L.K. Jr. Center for Nonviolent Social Change, undated (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Martin Luther King Center for Non-Violent Social Change: Meeting Files, Board of Directors and Executive Committee, 1971-1980 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Martin Luther King Center for Non-Violent Social Change: Meeting Files, Board of Directors, 1980 January 10-16 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Martin Luther King Center for Non-Violent Social Change: Newsletter, M.L.K. Jr. Center for Nonviolent Social Change, 1974 January-1979 (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Martin Luther King Center for Non-Violent Social Change: News Release, New Coalition of Conscience, 1983 January 13 (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - Martin Luther King Center for Non-Violent Social Change: Pamphlet, "I Have A Dream Celebration", 1982 (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - Martin Luther King Center for Non-Violent Social Change: Report, Board of Directors, 1990 April 19 (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - Martin Luther King Center for Non-Violent Social Change: Statement, MLK Jr. Center for Nonviolent Social Change, 1973 (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - Model Inner City Community Organization (MICCO): Organizational Description, MICCO, Circa 1971 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Model Inner City Community Organization (MICCO): Article, Helen Sheffield, 1973 June 11 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Model Inner City Community Organization (MICCO): Blueprints, Northwest Urban Renewal Project, Circa 1978 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Model Inner City Community Organization (MICCO): Booklet, Design Objectives, 1971 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Model Inner City Community Organization (MICCO): Brochure, MICCO and You, undated (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Model Inner City Community Organization (MICCO): Clippings, MICCO and Shaw Urban Renewal Area, 1970-1972 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Model Inner City Community Organization (MICCO): Contract, Agreement MICCO and Ethel Murry, Circa 1971 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Model Inner City Community Organization (MICCO): Contract, Draft MICCO and RLA, 1972 January 14 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Model Inner City Community Organization (MICCO): Correspondence, MICCO Housing Committee, 1963 March 06 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Model Inner City Community Organization (MICCO): Correspondence, Dr. King and Shaw Urban Renewal Area, 1967 March 23 (Box 24, Folder 10)